Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Records WAG.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1944-2006
  - My Life on the Streets by Joe Homeless, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - National Alliance against Racist and Political Repression: Fifth Annual Human Rights Awards Luncheon, Oct 21, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - National Association of Black Social Workers, 1989, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Social Workers (NASW): A Study of Attitudes of NASW Members, Lapsed Members and Non-Members, Aug 16, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - NASW Delegate Assembly, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - NASW National Conference, 1985, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - NASW National Conference, Sep 9, 1987-Sep 12, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - NASW National Conference, Nov 9, 1988-Nov 12, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - NASW National Conference, Oct 11, 1989-Oct 14, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NASW National Conference, Nov 14, 1990-Nov 17, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - NASW: New York City Chapter, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NASW: New York City Chapter (includes conference on "Crossing the Picket Line: Do We or Don't We?"), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NASW: New York City Chapter, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NASW: New York City Chapter Newsletter, Currents, 1982-1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NASW: Professional Advancement Travel Service, Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - National Federation of Social Service Employees, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - National Welfare Rights Movement, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Neponsit Home for the Aged: Institutional Aides, 1977-1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - New Management in Human Services: Various Chapters Including "Applying Modern Management Concepts to Social Work" by Leon H. Goldberg, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - New Member Information and Related Materials, 1960s-1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - New York City Budget for Fiscal Year 1995: Correspondence, Notes and Related Materials, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - New York City Budget for Fiscal Year 1995: Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - New York City Council: Correspondence, Resolutions, 1987-1996 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - New York City Council Four Year Financial Plan, Nov 21, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - New York City Council Management Reforms and Productivity Savings, Nov 15, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - New York City Department of Health: Employee Rosters and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - New York City Department of Labor: Correspondence, 1958-1966 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - New York City Department of Personnel: Correspondence, Policy and Procedure Updates, 1956-1968, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - New York City Department of Social Services: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - New York City Department of Welfare: Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - New York City "Doomsday" Budget (Mayor Dinkins): Press Clippings, Correspondence, and Related Materials, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - New York City "Doomsday" Budget (Mayor Giuliani): Press Clippings, Correspondence, and Related Materials, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation: General, 1976-1982, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - New York City Housing Authority: general, 1983-1987, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - New York City Summary of Fiscal Year 1997 Executive Budget prepared by DC 37, AFSCME, May 9, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - New York City Union Pact Press Clippings, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, Oct 26, 1969-Oct 28, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, Aug 30, 1992-Sep 3, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - New York State Department of Health, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - New York State Department of Labor, 1985, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - New York State Executive Budget: Alternative Budget Proposals (includes New York City and national proposals), 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - New York State Executive Budget: Statistical and Narrative Summary Fiscal Year April 1, 1989 to March 31, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New York State Public Employees Federation: Constitution and By-Laws, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter: Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter: Citywide Coordinating Committee of Welfare Groups, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter: Community Action The Organizer, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Newsletter: Crisis Intervention Services, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter: New York Labor, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Newsletter: The Advance, the Voice of the Workers, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Newsletter: The Facts, a Biweekly Letter to the Community, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Newsletter: Welfare Local 371 C.I.O. News, 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Newsletter: Welfare Local 371 News, Three Seventy One News, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - No False Alarm: Brooklyn's Response to the Fire Department's Budget (Draft), Mar 21, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - North Star Fund: Five Years of Funding Social Change in NYC, 1979-1984 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Notices and Announcements, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1950-1953 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1961, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jan 1965-Jun 1965 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jul 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jan 1966-May 1966 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jun 1966-Dec 1966 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jan 1967-May 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jun 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jan 1969-Jun 1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Notices and Announcements, Jul 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Notices and Announcements, 1980s (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Notices of Examinations and Related Materials, 1967-2001 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - NOW! How to Start a Welfare Rights Organization, May 25, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Office Equipment: Correspondence and Assessment, 1972, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Office Renovations for 817 Broadway, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Officer and Staff Meetings, 1973, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Operating Budgets, 1968, 1970, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Operation Think Twice "OT2" A Television Commercial Campaign for Teenagers and Young Adults, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Organizational Newsletter, Dec 12, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Organizational Newsletter, Aug 16, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Organizational Newsletter, Apr 16, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Organizational Newsletter, Apr 1982-Jun 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Organizational Newsletter, Feb 1983-Apr 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Organizational Newsletter, Jun 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Newsletter (original layout and Related Materials), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Organizational Newsletter (original layout and Related Materials), 1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Organizational Newsletter, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Organizational Newsletter [becomes "Newsletter" on Jan. 18, 1991] (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - [Organizational] Newsletter, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - [Organizational] Newsletter, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - [Organizational] Newsletter, Jan 1994-Oct 1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - [Organizational] Newsletter (story lists), 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Organizational Report, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Organizers' Guides, 1962, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Organizing Manual, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Peace and Freedom Party, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Pension Guide, Prepared by Chuck Miller, May 1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Personnel Matters: Transcript of Discussion, Feb 24, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Petitions and Group Complaints, 1962-1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Position Paper on the Utilization of Case Aides, [1967?] (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Presentation Delivered by Richard Mendes, Brooklyn College and Columbia University, to the Welfare Fact Finding Panel, 23779 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Press Clippings: Articles on Local 371 (includes initial election of Charles Ensley, 1975-1996 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Press Clippings: Death of Jerry Wurf, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, Undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1962-1967 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1970-1978 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1981-1992 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Problems and Conflicts in the Bureau of Child Welfare, Sep 1, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Procedure and Informational Guide: Prepared by SSEU for Distribution to Department of Welfare Supervisors, Undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Progressive Labor Party, Trade Union Division: Flyers, 1960s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Project RESCU, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Proposal for Child Day Care Centers to Serve the Children of Union Members, Welfare Recipients and the Local Community, Undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Proposals (not collective bargaining) Regarding Services, Actions, Recommendations, 1965-1995 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Public Employees Federation (PEF), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations and Publicity, 1965, 1990s (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Recorded Union News, May 1972-Jul 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Recorded Union News, Aug 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Recorded Union News, Jan 1973-May 1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Recorded Union News, Jun 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Recorded Union News, Jan 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Recorded Union News, Jul 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Recorded Union News, Jul 1975-Aug 1975, Nov 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Recorded Union News, Jan 1976-May 1976 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Recorded Union News, Jun 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Recorded Union News, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Recorded Union News, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Recorded Union News, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Recorded Union News, Jan 1985-Jun 1985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Recorded Union News, Jul 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Recorded Union News, Jan 1986-Jun 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Recorded Union News, Jul 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Recorded Union News, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Recorded Union News, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Recorded Union News, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Recorded Union News, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Recorded Union News, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Recorded Union News, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Recorded Union News, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Recorded Union News, Jan 1994-Oct 1994 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Recorded Union News, Jun 1996-Jul 1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Recruitment Flyers, 1979-1981 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Recruitment Flyers, 1985-1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Recruitment Flyers, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Re-Election of Mayor John V. Lindsay, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Report: Emergency Situation at the Non-Residence Welfare Center, Feb 3, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Report: New York Report with Judith Mage on Channel 9 (Script), Nov 27, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Report: Reorganization of Income Maintenance and Service Operations in Department of Social Service Centers, [1976?] (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Report: Welfare Grants: Fixed Levels for Rent (Testimony), Mar 21, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Report on the Colloquium: Critical Issues for Labor-1986; Economic Development and Occupational Health and Safety, Dec 10, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Reports: Careers in Welfare, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Reports: Recommendations to the Commissioner of Welfare, Welfare Benefits, Wallen, Queens, and Others, 1965-1967 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Required Social Services: A Handbook for Public Assistance Caseworkers, 24593 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Retainer Agreement: Montalbano Initiatives Inc. (Consultant), 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Retirement: Issues, Parties and Related Materials, 1980s-1990s (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Sams Fund: To Aid Husband of Member Francine Sams, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - SCENE published by Welfare Employees Local 371, May 1965 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests A-C, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests D-F, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests G-I, 1967-1971 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests J-L, 1963-1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests M-O, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests P-R, 1967-1971 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests S-T, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Selective Service System: Occupational Deferment Requests U-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Shattered Lives: A Portrait of New York's Children as reported by Statewide Youth Advocacy, Inc., Rochester, New York, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Shelters: Guidelines for Proposals to Provide Shelters for Adults, Apr 1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Shelters: Regulations, Operations and Related Materials, [late 1990s?] (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Shelters: Press Clippings, 1985, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Singleton, Kitt (Vice President Auxiliary Titles): Work Outline Report, Sep 14, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - S. S. E. What It Is, Why Join It, [early 1960s?] (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Social Work Actions for Welfare Rights: Spring Series of Public Forums, Undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Social Work Month (March): Correspondence, Lists, Flyers and Related Materials, 1985-1992 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - South Africa: African National Congress, NY Anti-Apartheid Coordinating Council and Related Materials, 1985-1996 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Special Benefit Fund, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Special Services for Children, Sep 1984-Aug 1985 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Special Services for Children, Sep 1985-Feb 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Speech: Staff Problems in the New York City Department of Welfare, May 5, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - State Communities Aid Association (SCAA), 1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Statement by Dr. Jack R. Goldberg, Commissioner, City of New York Department of Social Services before the City Council of New York Special Committee of the HRA, Feb 14, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Statements: David N. Dinkins, Mayor, 1990, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Statements: General, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Statements: Stanley Hill, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Statements: Judith Mage, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Statements: Martin Morgenstern, 1967-1970 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Statements: Edward Perlmutter, Undated, 1967-1970 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Statements: Joseph Rogoff, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Statements: Joe Sperling, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Statements: Joseph Tepidino, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Statements, Remarks, Testimony: General, 1965-1996 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Staten Island Job Center Pilot Project, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Stewards: Correspondence, Lists, and Manual, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Strikes: 1965 Welfare Strike, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Strikes: 1965 Welfare Strike Bulletin (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Strikes: 1965 Welfare Strike Clippings, Jan 1965- Mar 1965 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Strikes: 1965 Welfare Strike Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Strikes: 1965 Welfare Strike Correspondence with Donations (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Strikes: 1965 Welfare Strike 20th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Strikes: 1967 Welfare Strike, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Strikes: General, Clippings, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Strikes: General, Support from SSEU, 1968-1985 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Student Multicultural Leadership Project, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Supervisor I, II and III Lists, 1966, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Supervisors: General, 1980s-1996 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Task and Standards Master List, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Task Force: Unions Meeting, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Telegrams (mostly strike related), 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Telegrams, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Telegrams, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Telegrams, 1968, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Territory Assignments, 1989, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - This is Welfare Local 371 pamphlet, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - This We Believe…: A Statement of Principles and Program for the Responsible Administration of AFSCME by Jerry Wurf and Gordon W. Chapman, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - To the New Caseworkers: An Introduction to the SSEU, [1960s] (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Trade Union Leadership Institute: Why Unions Are In Trouble…And What They Can Do About It, [1989?] (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Transfer Policy, 1958, 1965-1966, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Union Dues, 1965-1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Union Dues, 1974-1977, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Unionist: Accounting, 1972-1976, 1987, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Unionist: Bookbinder Associates correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Unionist: Copy, layout, original artwork, 1982-1987, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Unionis t: Correspondence, 1969, 1985-1989, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Unionist: Personals, 1985-1986, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - United Farm Workers: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1967-1968, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Welfare: We Work with the Homeless: Suggestions from the Men and Women Who Work with the Homeless in New York City, Undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Welfare: General, Press Clippings and Related Material, 1962-1998 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Welfare: Reform (New Welfare Law), Press Clippings and Related Material, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Welfare: Reform ("Pendulum Swings Back"), Press Clippings and Related Material, 1997-1999 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Welfare: Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF), Press Clippings, Correspondence and Related Material, 2000-2002 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Welfare Fund: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1960s (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Fund: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970-1974 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Fund: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Welfare Fund: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980s, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Welfare Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees' Meetings, 1966-1968 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Welfare Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees' Meetings (including joint meetings with Educational Fund), 1969-1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees' Meetings (including joint meetings with Educational Fund), 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees' Meetings (including joint meetings with Educational Fund), 1974-1977 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Fund: Minutes, Board of Trustees' Meetings (including joint meetings with Educational Fund), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Fund: Pensions and Benefits, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965-1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Fund: Trustee Election and related issues, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Workers Committee for Peace in Vietnam and Related Organizations, 1965-1969, 1983-1986 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Workers' Compensation, 1985, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Working Theatre: Programs, Correspondence, Press Clippings, 1986-1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Working with Narcotics Addicts: A Report from the Amsterdam Drug Workers, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - World Trade Center Attacks Aftermath: Correspondence, Press Clippings, Health and Related Guidelines, Workers' Assistance Bulletins, Sep 2001-Dec 2001 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - World Trade Union Congress (11th), Sep 16, 1986-Sep 22, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Wurf, Jerry (Regional Director, Executive Director, International President AFSCME): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1957-1974 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Wurf, Jerry: Memorial Program, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Youth Council Bureau, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Series II: Bargaining Files and Related Arbitration Cases, 1938-1996
    - About the OCB(Office of Collective Bargaining), Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Advisory Arbitration Panel Resolution, Jun 28, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Advisory Recommendations, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Agreement between Office and Professional Employees International Union and SSEU Local 371, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Amended Agreement, Sep 4, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Arbitration Awards, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Arbitration Decision, Recommendations, Memorandum of Understanding, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Arbitration re: Workload, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Brief in Defense of Retirement and Pensions, [1967?] (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Brief in Support of Demands, Oct 29, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Brief in Support of Educational Fund, Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW) Caseload Demands for Jan 1, 1965-Dec 31, 1966 Contract (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW) Caseworker's and Children's Counselor's Collective Bargaining Program: Draft, Aug 1966 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Caseworker's Collective Bargaining Program, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Certification: Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1958-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Children's Counselors Collective Bargaining Program, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - City of New York v. District Council 37: Decision No. B-4-69, Docket No. BCB-45-49, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - City of New York v. District Council 37: Decision No. B-12-72, Docket No. BCB-114-72, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - City of New York v. AFSCME, District Council 37: Docket No. A-487-75 Award, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - City of New York v. SSEU: Case No. E67-1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - City of New York v. Social Service Employees Union (SSEU): Decision No. B-11-68, Docket No. BCB-22-68, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - City of New York v. Social Service Employees Union (SSEU): Fact-Finding/Transcripts, Jan 23, 1967-Jan 24, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - City of New York v. SSEU: Fact-Finding/Transcripts, Jan 25, 1967-Jan 31, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - City of New York v. SSEU: Report and Recommendations, Mar 15, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - City of New York v. SSEU: Report and Recommendations, Apr 25, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - City of New York v. SSEU: Summer Work Week Schedule, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - City of New York v. SSEU, Local 371: Decision No. B-4-72, Docket No. BCB-95-71, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)